<resources>
    <string name="app_name">BolognaTourGuide</string>

    <string name="attraction_content_description">Attraction</string>
    <string name="title">Title</string>
    <string name="address">Address</string>

    <string name="tamburini_title">Tamburini</string>
    <string name="tamburini_address">Via Caprarie, 1</string>
    <string name="tamburini_desc">The Tamburini Shop offers a wide selection of typical regional and Italian meats and cheeses, Restaurant,
        Self-service restaurants and more!</string>

    <string name="fourghetti_title">Fourghetti</string>
    <string name="fourghetti_address">Via Augusto Murri, 71</string>
    <string name="fourghetti_desc">The restaurant of the famous Chef Bruno Barbieri, 7 michelin stars</string>

    <string name="laverace_title">Pizzeria La Verace</string>
    <string name="laverace_address">Via Cairoli, 16</string>
    <string name="laverace_desc">Neapolitan pizza and Mediterranean dishes among rough white walls with exposed stone
        and suggestive cave room.</string>

    <string name="villaghigi_title">Parco di Villa Ghigi</string>
    <string name="villaghigi_address">Via San Mamolo 105</string>
    <string name="villaghigi_desc">Villa Ghigi is a public park in Bologna, located close to the urban area. Part of the park is used for agricultural
        land and, recently, for grazing.</string>

    <string name="viagiardini_title">Parco di Via dei Giardini (della Ca\' Bura)</string>
    <string name="viagiardini_address">Via dei Giardini</string>
    <string name="viagiardini_desc">It extends over 9 hectares around a central axis that connects a square between two large artificial hills
         paved with a gazebo that juts out over a large stretch of water. The pond is the heart of the park and recalls the era in which around the Navile
         clay kilns and quarries flourished.</string>

    <string name="giardinimargherita_title">Giardini Margherita</string>
    <string name="giardinimargherita_address">Piazza di Porta Santo Stefano</string>
    <string name="giardinimargherita_desc">It is the largest and most popular city park. Designed by Sambuy from Piedmont, to provide Bologna with a
        large public green space based on the example of the major Italian and European cities, it was inaugurated in 1879 with the name of Passeggio
        Regina Margherita (as a tribute to the wife of Umberto I).</string>

    <string name="sanpetronio_title">Basilica di San Petronio</string>
    <string name="sanpetronio_address">Piazza Galvani, 5</string>
    <string name="sanpetronio_desc">The Basilica of San Petronio is the main church of Bologna: it dominates the Piazza Maggiore and, although it is
        largely unfinished, it is one of the largest churches in Europe. Its imposing size makes it the fourth largest church in Italy.</string>

    <string name="nettuno_title">Statua del Nettuno</string>
    <string name="nettuno_address">Piazza del Nettuno</string>
    <string name="nettuno_desc">The Neptune fountain, nicknamed al Żigànt (Gigante in Italian: Giant in English) in the Bolognese dialect due to the
        size of the statue of Neptune, is located in Bologna in piazza del Nettuno.</string>

    <string name="torri_title">Torri degli Asinelli-Garisenda</string>
    <string name="torri_address">Piazza di Porta Ravegnana</string>
    <string name="torri_desc">The Garisenda and Asinelli tower are the so-called two towers of Bologna, symbol of the city, located at the intersection
        of the ancient streets San Donato (now via Zamboni), San Vitale, Maggiore, Santo Stefano and Castiglione.</string>

    <string name="museo_civico_title">Museo Civico Archeologico</string>
    <string name="museo_civico_address">Via dell\'Archiginnasio 2</string>
    <string name="museo_civico_desc">The museum is one of the most important Italian archaeological collections and is highly representative of
        local history, from prehistory to the Roman age. His collection of Egyptian antiquities is one of the most important in Europe.
        Between 1972 and 2012 the Museum hosted over 150 exhibitions and exhibitions of an archaeological and artistic nature.</string>

    <string name="museo_resistenza_title">Museo della Resistenza di Bologna</string>
    <string name="museo_resistenza_address">Via Sant\'Isaia 20</string>
    <string name="museo_resistenza_desc">The Museum of the Resistance of Bologna is located in the convent complex of San Mattia and collects
        different types of material (archive documents, photographs, posters, multimedia products) related to the history of anti-fascism,
        the Bolognese Resistance and republican Italy.</string>

    <string name="museo_storia_title">Museo della Storia di Bologna</string>
    <string name="museo_storia_address">Via Castiglione 8</string>
    <string name="museo_storia_desc">TPalazzo Pepoli, also known as the Museums of History of Bologna, is a historic building located in the
        center of Bologna near the two towers, in Via Castiglione.</string>

    <string name="attraction_detail_description">Description</string>
    <string name="category_restaurants">Restaurants</string>
    <string name="category_parks">Parks</string>
    <string name="category_cultures">Cultures</string>
    <string name="category_museums">Museums</string>

</resources>
